[{"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把地上跑的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 5, 11], 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把水里游的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 8, 9], 3], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把水里游的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 4, 7, 9, 11], 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把地上跑的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L3.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海马_L1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 1, 4, 5, 6, 7], 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把天上飞的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L3.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 8], 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把天上飞的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 3, 7, 8], 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把水里游的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L3.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 3, 4, 6, 10, 11], 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把水里游的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 1, 7, 9, 10], 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把地上跑的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "swim", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 2, 3, 8, 9], 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把天上飞的动物选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}], "unit": "只", "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 4, 5, 6, 8], 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-09"}]